From Wikipedia:

The International Astronomical Union (IAU) defined the galactic coordinate system in reference to the Equatorial coordinate system in 1958[2] The north galactic pole is defined to be at right ascension 12h 49m, declination +27.4° (B1950), and the zero of longitude is the great semicircle that originates from this point along the line in position angle 123° with respect to the equatorial pole. The galactic longitude increases in the same direction as right ascension. Galactic latitude is positive towards the north galactic pole, the poles themselves at ±90° and the galactic equator being zero.[3]

The equivalent system referred to as J2000 has the north galactic pole at 12h 51m 26.282s +27° 07′ 42.01″ (J2000), the zero of longitude at the position angle of 122.932°.[4] The point in the sky at which the galactic latitude and longitude are both zero is 17h 45m 37.224s −28° 56′ 10.23″ (J2000). This is offset slightly from the radio sourceSagittarius A*, which is the best physical marker of the true galactic center. Sagittarius A* is located at 17h 45m 40.04s −29° 00′ 28.1″ (J2000), or galactic longitude 359° 56′ 39.4″, galactic latitude −0° 2′ 46.2″.[citation needed]

Translation:

Let G be the galactic frame, so Galactic North is g3 and galactic latitude and longitude are both zero in the direction of g1.  Then

g3 expressed in J2000:  RA = 192.85950833 deg, Dec = 27.12833611 deg
g3 = [-0.867665382947348  -0.198076649977489   0.455985113757595]

g1 expressed in J2000:  RA = 266.4051 deg, Dec = -28.936175 deg
g1 = [-0.0548739561755390  -0.8734371822248346  -0.4838350314319811]

g2 = g3xg1 = [0.494110775064704  -0.444828614979805   0.746981957785302]